uahoy.com 2015-08-31

# 

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services, mobile apps and websites offered by Ahoy Telecom Private Limited or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. However, at times, we may post product specific privacy notices to explain our products in more detail.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website www.ahoy.co.in or write it to us at:

**Ahoy Telecom Private Limited**  
B-13, First Floor,  
Sector 64,  
Noida 201301,  
U.P, India  
Telephone: +91 120 4574737

**Information we collect and how we use it**  
We may collect the following types of information: 

  * **Information you provide -** When you register with us, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Ahoy services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * **Cookies -** When you visit Ahoy, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Ahoy also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web and on other Ahoy services. 
  * **User communications -** When you send email or other communications to Ahoy, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services. 
  * **Affiliated Ahoy Services on other sites -** We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Ahoy in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. 
  * **Third Party Applications -** Ahoy may make available third party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by Ahoy when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies. 
  * **Location data -** Ahoy offers location-enabled services, such mobile contextual LBS services. If you use those services, Ahoy may receive information about your actual location (such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device) or information that can be used to approximate a location (such as a cell ID).  
In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to: 
  * **Unique application number -** Certain services include a unique application number that is not associated with your account or you. This number and information about your installation (e.g., operating system type, version number) may be sent to Ahoy when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers (for example, to request automatic updates to the software). 
  * Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services 
  * Protect the rights or property of Ahoy or our users.  
If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.  
Ahoy processes personal information on our servers in India and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information outside your own country.  
**Choices**  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Ahoy features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.  
**Information sharing**  
Ahoy only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Ahoy in the following limited circumstances: 
  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Ahoy, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
If Ahoy becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
**Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption, where needed and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
We restrict access to personal information to Ahoy employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.  
**Accessing and updating personal information**  
When you use Ahoy services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.   
**Enforcement**  
Ahoy complies with the data protection act which comes under Jurisdiction of Indian Law and operated and set-up by Indian Government, regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information  
Ahoy regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is Ahoy's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Ahoy and an individual.   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
